it4profit.com 2002-12-23

# IT4profit - b2b exchange for IT distributors

**IT4profit B2B EXCHANGE PRIVACY POLICY**

 **1\. OVERVIEW**

 **1.1 General**  
e-Vision Limited (hereinafter called "Exchange Operator"), as an operator of real-time trading facilities and B2B exchange at www.IT4profit.com and all related and successor websites (collectively, “IT4profit” TM), is committed to protecting the privacy of IT4profit users. IT4profit is the Business-to-Business Exchange for the online activity of legal entities, not private consumers or end-users. A company is the user of IT4profit. IT4profit business model allows combine several companies, which belong to one corporation and its business partner network, into a Business Group. The Company belongs only to one Business Group. The Business Group is a virtually separate business not visible within the limits of this Group, if inter Business Groups Trade Partner Agreement is not signed. Every Business Group has one company-owner. The Business Group owner signs IT4profit B2B Exchange Membership Agreement and is the owner of IT4profit license. 

**1.2 Principles**  
Exchange Operator supports Business Group model at IT4profit and declares no public customers which can be accessible by any participant of the Exchange and no public suppliers which are allowed to trade their goods or services to registered or non registered participants of IT4profit. The Privacy Policy guarantees that customers and suppliers of each individual Company are privately held business partners of this Company. Any contact, finance, logistics and other information about company’s supplier or customer is visible to the Company only, not for anyone else at IT4profit. Business transactions held by the Company and business partners are kept private and confidential and cannot be accessed by any other participant of IT4profit. 

Exchange Operator places the highest priority on protecting the privacy of IT4profit registered Business Groups ("Members"), Business Group's authorized companies-users ("User"), as well as others who visit ("Visitors") this IT4profit website at www.IT4profit.com (the "Site"). However, this site is designed for Companies and adult Visitors of IT4profit, and is not intended for use by children under 13. Because Exchange Operator gathers certain types of information on the Site, this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") outlines the general terms and conditions surrounding what information Exchange Operator collects and how it is used. By registering as a Member, becoming a User and visiting our Site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

**1.3 Agreements**  
Please note that the posted Membership Agreement and agreements specific to an IT4profit service may contain other terms that deal specifically with a Member's confidential information. This Privacy Policy is not intended to cover postings on the Community Areas of the Site such as public chats, help and discussion boards. 

**2\. COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION BY EXCHANGE OPERATOR**

 **2.1 Contact and User Information**  
In order to become a User of the non-public content at IT4profit, you must first register and submit a variety of contact and user information. If necessary, Exchange Operator reserves the right to disclose the names of Users to other Users of IT4profit who are employed by the same Member (Business Group). Exchange Operator uses the Contact and User Information to communicate information regarding: (a) new and modified services and features offered by Exchange Operator; (b) special offers made available by Exchange Operator; (c) specific activities in which the Users are participating and (d) activities of related or interested Users with the same corporation. The Contact and User Information is also used to process and ship orders placed by the User. 

**2.2 Visit Data**  
When a User or Visitor accesses IT4profit, Exchange Operator collects, records and retains general non-personally identifiable data about such usage of IT4profit including but not limited to the User's or Visitor's domain name, the IP address, the name of the Web page from which each entered IT4profit, the locations each visits within IT4profit, and the amount of time spent on each page of IT4profit (collectively, "Data"). Exchange Operator uses this Data to determine the demographics of Users or Visitors, to analyse trends and to develop and distribute to third parties aggregate statistics and general information about IT4profit. Exchange Operator will not disclose information that identifies specific Users or transactions, except as noted above in "Contact and User Information." 

**2.3 Cookies**  
Like most web sites, IT4profit utilizes cookie technology. "Cookies" are pieces of data sent from a Web server to a Web browser that enable a Web server to identify users that visit a site hosted by the server. Exchange Operator uses Cookies in order to recognize returning Users and Visitors to IT4profit so that Exchange Operator can provide more customized information and services to its Users and Visitors. To disable the use of Cookies by your browser, review your browser's preferences and options. 

**2.4 Other Information**  
As a Visitor or User, you may choose to send Exchange Operator a question via e-mail, register for a special service or otherwise communicate with Exchange Operator, such as voluntarily participating in a survey. Exchange Operator may also use such information to communicate with Users and to enhance IT4profit, in an effort to better meet the needs of Users. 

**2.5 Member Information Disclosure**  
Upon request, Exchange Operator may disclose to a Member (Active Participant) the activities of its authorized Users on the Site, including providing Contact and User Information and other information collected by Exchange Operator to the Member (Active Participant) corporation. 

**2.6 Aggregate Data**  
Exchange Operator may extract information that does not identify specific Users or transactions (collectively, "Aggregate Data") from Contact and User Information, Data, Cookies, and other information collected on the Site and use such Aggregate Data for internal and/or commercial purposes. 

**3\. THIRD PARTY RELATIONSHIPS WITH EXCHANGE OPERATOR**

 **3.1 Providers**  
Exchange Operator has relationships with various third party providers to maintain and provide services to IT4profit. These third parties are all bound by confidentiality agreements that protect the privacy of the IT4profit Users, must utilize information solely for the purpose of providing services on behalf of Exchange Operator and are bound to keep any personally identifiable information they receive secure. 

**3.2 Links**  
IT4profit provides links to other web sites maintained by third parties unrelated to Exchange Operator. Please be aware that if you link to another third-party web site, that site is not subject to Exchange Operator's Privacy Policy, and Exchange Operator has no control over the use of information disclosed on such sites. Exchange Operator is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. Exchange Operator encourages its Users to be aware when they leave the Site and suggests that Users read the privacy policies of each site visited. 

**4\. SECURITY MEASURES**

 **4.1 General**  
Exchange Operator and its third party providers have implemented extensive security measures to help protect against the risk of loss, misuse and alteration of any information under Exchange Operator's control including using encryption, limiting employee access, and using industry-standard controls such as firewalls and secure environments for personally identifiable information. 

**4.2 Member Security**  
Additionally, in order to protect the security and integrity of the proprietary and confidential information of IT4profit's Members (Business Groups) and Members' Users that interact on the non-public portion of IT4profit, Exchange Operator has taken the following actions, among many others, to ensure that IT4profit meets the strict security needs of IT4profit's Members: 

  * Exchange Operator makes initial activation of a Business Group, company owner of a Business Group and a Business Group Administrator. 
  * Access to the Business Group Administration role is limited by ID and password. Access to the ID can be limited only from some range of IP addresses. 
  * Only the responsible person from the company owner with the Business Group Administrator role has access to the other Business Group participants’ information.
  * Every Business Group participant company has a company administrator role. The initial activation of the participant company and its administrator is made by the Business Group Administrator. The initial activation of the company users IDs and users passwords are made by the company administrator. The company administrator can limit access to some user ID only from some range of IP address.
  * Business Group can publish its business to other Business Groups by signing online Trade Partner Agreement (TPA). The level of information limited visibility and all other regulations are determined by TPA. 

**(a) Security Policy.** Exchange Operator has adopted and enforced a Security Policy to protect all proprietary and confidential information of IT4profit's Members. The Security Policy addresses information classification, information security procedures (electronic and hard copy information), limited disclosure procedures, physical facility access and general security awareness and enforcement. All member information is classified as "highly confidential" under the corporate security policy. Exchange Operator has developed and adheres to strict security policies and guidelines with all of Exchange Operator’s third-party data hosting facilities providers. 

**(b) Authentication.** Exchange Operator has deployed industry standard Member authentication and user verification procedures to limit access to Member information to only those participants that our Members authorize. 

**4.3 Disclaimer**  
Notwithstanding Exchange Operator's extensive efforts, such security measures may not prevent all loss, misuse or alteration of information disclosed on the Site. 

**5\. PROCEDURE FOR ACCESSING AND CORRECTING INFORMATION**

Users can access their Contact and User Information, and other appropriate Member-identifiable information collected by Exchange Operator by contacting Exchange Operator as set forth in the IT4profit Contact section of the Site. If a User believes there are factual errors in such information, the User may contact IT4profit Administrator and/or Member's (Business Group) Administrator and detail the inaccurate information. Exchange Operator and/or Member's (Business Group) Administrator will verify and correct any factual errors within a reasonable time. 

**6\. OPTING OUT OF MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS**

Users may choose whether to receive direct marketing communications relating to IT4profit at the time of registration. If a User subsequently does not want to receive information about special offers available through IT4profit, User may unsubscribe by sending an email to support@IT4profit.com with "Remove Me" in the subject line. 

**7\. PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES**

Exchange Operator may update or amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. All updates to this policy will be posted here. Check here periodically to see if the Privacy Policy has changed. 

Last update: October 22, 2001
